let questions = [
	{
		num: 1,
		question: 'React JS is a library for- ?',
		answer: `Building reusable UI's and components`,
		options : [
      "Controlling server side interactions on clouds",
      "Attempting XSS and breaching CORS",
      "Building reusable UI's and components",
      "Rendering HTML DOM elements and CSS extension"
    ]
	},
	{
		num: 2,
		question: 'The useEffect hook in React- ?',
		answer: `Runs a specified function once state changes`,
		options : [
			"Runs a specified function once state changes",
      "Creates a stateful value",
      "Handles Fetch requests once state changes",
      "Re-renders a component once state changes"
    ]
	},
	{
		num: 3,
		question: `In TypeScript, \n const i: number = 0, is an example of- ?`,
		answer: `Explicit Type Declaration`,
		options : [
			"Implicit Type Declaration",
      "Explicit Type Declaration",
      "Generic Initialization",
      "Modular Exporting"
    ]
	},
	{
		num: 4,
		question: `Decode the RegEx: /^[a-z\d]{5,12}$/`,
		answer: `Any letter and digit character 5 - 12 times`,
		options : [
			"All letters of the alphabet and numbers 5 - 12",
      "Any letter of the alphabet at least 5 times and at most 12 times",
      "Any letter and digit character 5 - 12 times",
      "Only a caret, alphabets, number 5 - 12 & a dollar sign is permitted"
    ]
	},
	{
		num: 5,
		question: `In Vue JS, Two way data binding can be achieved using-`,
		answer: `Using v-model`,
		options : [
			"Using v-if and v-else",
      "Using the composition API",
      "Using the options API",
      "Using v-model"
    ]
	},
	{
		num: 6,
		question: `Using 'ref' in the vue composition API will-`,
		answer: `Make an element will be reactive`,
		options : [
			"Render an element to a preferred position",
      "Make an element will be reactive",
      "Store a reference to a DOM element",
      "Refer to a specified JSON endpoint"
    ]
	},
	{
		num: 7,
		question: `Asynchronous Javascript Code can be thought of as-`,
		answer: `A way to eliminate the single threaded code nature of Javascript`,
		options : [
			"Code that should run before others are executed",
			"A way to eliminate the single threaded code nature of Javascript",
      "A modern method of accessing a database",
      "A way to implement modern ES6 features"
    ]
	},
	{
		num: 8,
		question: `In projects involving NPM, the package.json file usually-`,
		answer: `Stores all your project's dependencies and information`,
		options : [
			"Permits data to be read without making multiple requests",
			"Stores all your project's dependencies and information",
      "Serves as a key to access NPM resources",
      "Eliminates run time issues and bugs"
    ]
	},
	{
		num: 9,
		question: `Functional programming is a paradigm which-`,
		answer: `Is a subset of declarative programming and all data is treated as immutable`,
		options : [
			"Is a subset of imperative programming and all data is treated as immutable",
			"Data is treated as mutable",
			"Functions are written using arrow functions",
      "Is a subset of declarative programming and all data is treated as immutable"
    ]
	},
	{
		num: 10,
		question: `AJAX is-`,
		answer: `A technique for loading data into a part of a page without refreshing the page`,
		options : [
			"A pattern used for checking browser - server status",
			"A paradigm utilized only in Single Page Applications",
			"A technique for loading data into a part of a page without refreshing the page",
      "A modern XML and XHTML format"
    ]
	},
]
